Educational Technology Services Records UA245
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Educational Technology Services Records
2014 -- 2017
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
UA245
626 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
This collection contains the records of Educational Technology Services.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Educational Technology Services, 2017.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in one series: Great Courses.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Educational Technology Services (ETS) is a department within Tufts Technology Services. Members of ETS are trained to help Tufts faculty and staff of courses to incorporate technology into their academic programs. ETS also leads workshops throughout the school-year for faculty to learn new technologies. As of 2017, the department is led by Paul Bergen, Director of Educational Technology and Learning Spaces. Starting in 2010 and in following years, the group quickly gained importance across all four Tufts campus', as integrating technology into the classroom became vital for engaging and connecting with students. Projects undertaken have included supporting instructors with "Instructional Continuity" when a class is cancelled, as well as helping faculty adjust to changes in university-wide learning management systems. ETS has also helped instructors to make course resources accessible to students, aiding with the publishing of lecture videos and notes through different platforms.
Related Materials
Blackboard Course Management System, 2000-2011. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Related Materials
University Information Technology Records, 1988-2012. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material relating to Great Courses at Tufts, including PDF files of assignments, bibliographies, focus questions, notes, slides, and the syllabus for Philosophy 167, as well as video files of the class lectures.
Information Systems; Curriculum and Instruction -- Teaching Material
- Great Courses, 2014 -- 2017; UA245.001; 626 Digital Object(s); 1 Web sites
  Conditions Governing Access
  Slides are available to Tufts Community users only. Non-Tufts users may request access using 'add to list.'
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by Educational Technology Services, 2017, accession UA-2018-021.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains PDF files of assignments, bibliographies, focus questions, notes, slides, and the syllabus for Philosophy 167, as well as video files of the class lectures. It also contains a webcrawl of the website conducted in 2017 that can be made available to members of the Tufts community in the DCA reading room.
  - Assignment 1 for Philosophy 167., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.584
    Open for research.
    Prepare a "legal brief" (5 to 7 pages long) for someone charged with judging Galileo.
  - Assignment 2 for Philosophy 167., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.585
    Write a 5 to 7 page paper comparing the evidence available as of 1651 for the law of free fall, the law of parabolic trajectory, and the law of inertia, respectively.
  - Assignment 3 for Philosophy 167., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.586
    In a brief paper (5-7 pages) explain what difference Halley would have said the purely mathematical discoveries presented in the De Motu made to the evidential status first of Kepler's "laws" and second of the "laws" of free-fall, projectile motion, and what we now call inertia.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 1., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.626
    Class one readings: supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 2., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.627
    Class two readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 3., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.628
    Class three readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 4., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.629
    Class four readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 5., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.630
    Class five readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 6., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.631
    Class six readings: supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 7., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.632
    Class seven readings: supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 8., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.633
    Class eight readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 9., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.634
    Class nine readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 10., 2014-10-07; gc.phil167.635
    Class ten readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 11., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.636
    Class eleven readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 12., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.637
    Class twelve readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 13., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.638
    Class thirteen readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Bibliography to Philosophy 167: Class 14., 2014-11-0; gc.phil167.639
    Class fourteen readings: assigned and supplemental.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 2., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.587
    Assignment for September 9 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe. Readings and 7 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 3., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.588
    Assignment for September 16 Kepler's Astronomia Nova and the Orbit of Mars. Readings and 4 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 4., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.589
    Assignment for September 23 Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables. Readings and 5 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 5., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.590
    Assignment for September 30 Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642. Readings and 6 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 6., 2014-10-07; gc.phil167.591
    Assignment for October 7 Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Motion. Readings and 5 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 7., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.592
    Assignment for October 14 Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion. Readings and 6 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 8., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.593
    Assignment for October 21 Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion. Readings and 6 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 9., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.594
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 10., 2014-11-0; gc.phil167.595
    Assignment for November 4 Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics. Readings and 6 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 11., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.596
    Assignment for November 18 Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684. Readings and 5 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 12., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.597
    Assignment for November 25 Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics. Readings and 6 focus questions.
  - Focus Questions for Philosophy 167: Class 13., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.598
    Assignment for December 2 Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum, Version 1. Readings and 7 focus questions.
  - Initial Paper Assignment for Philosophy 167., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.583
    Initial assignment for a short (2-3) page paper. Think of this exercise as an initial attempt to state the evidence problem posed by the three "chief world systems" as understood in 1600.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Complete., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.174
    Synopsis: Overview of the course -- Astronomy, as inherited by Ptolemy -- Ptolemy's Almagest -- Some philosophical issues -- Select sources. Section: Class 1, Complete.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 1., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.175
    Synopsis: 1510-1810: The "Scientific Revolution" -- The "Newtonian Revolution": the Principia -- A Course in the Philosophy of Science -- Reasons for Focusing on Newton's Principia -- Pedagogical Objectives Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 1.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 2., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.176
    Synopsis: The Celestial Sphere -- Planets: "Wandering Stars". Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 2.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 3., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.177
    Synopsis: The Problem of the Planets -- Classical Greek Solutions. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 3.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 4., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.178
    Synopsis: The Problem of the Planets -- Classical Greek Solutions. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 4.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 5., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.179
    Synopsis: Classical Greek Solutions -- Classical Greek Solutions After Aristotle. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 5.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 6., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.180
    Synopsis: Classical Greek Solutions After Aristotle. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 6.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 7., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.181
    Synopsis: Classical Greek Solutions After Aristotle -- The Problem Inherited by Ptolemy -- Ptolemy's Almagest: Overview of the Book. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 7.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 8., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.182
    Synopsis: Ptolemy's Almagest: Overview of the Book -- General Remarks on the System. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 8.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 9., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.183
    Synopsis: Ptolemy's Almagest: General Remarks on the System -- The Account of the Sun -- The Account of the Moon -- The Problem of Planetary Motion for Ptolemy. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 9.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 10., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.184
    Synopsis: Ptolemy's Almagest: The Problem of Planetary Motion for Ptolemy. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 10.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 11., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.185
    Synopsis: Ptolemy's Almagest: Ptolemy's Model of Planetary Motion -- The Achievement of Ptolemaic Astronomy. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 11.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 12., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.186
    Synopsis: Ptolemy's Almagest: Ptolemy's Model of Planetary Motion -- The Achievement of Ptolemaic Astronomy. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 12.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 13., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.187
    Synopsis: Ptolemy's Almagest: Ptolemy's Model of Planetary Motion -- The Achievement of Ptolemaic Astronomy. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 14.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 14., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.188
    Synopsis: The Achievement of Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Shortcomings of Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Introduction: Ptolemy as Bad Science? -- Issue: What Claim is Ptolemaic Theory Making? -- Issue: Is It Bad Because It Is Too Complicated? -- Issue: Is It Bad Because It Is Simply False? -- Issue: Is It Bad Because It Is Too Inaccurate? -- Select Sources. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 14.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Complete., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.189
    Synopsis: The Copernican Revolution -- De Revolutionibus Orbium Coelstium (1543) -- Tycho Brahe and Observational Astronomy -- The Crisis in "Mathematical" Astronomy -- Select Sources. Section: Class 2, Complete.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 1., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.190
    Synopsis: Ptolemaic Astronomy: e.g. Longtitudes of Mars -- A Problem Raised for Philosophy of Science -- Background: 13 Centuries of Ptolemaic Astronomy. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 1.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 2 - Part 3., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.191
    Synopsis: Background: 13 Centuries of Ptolemaic Astronomy -- 15th Century Planetary Astronomy: Regiomantanus. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 2 - 3.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 4., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.192
    Synopsis: 15th Century Planetary Astronomy: Regiomantanus -- Nicolaus Copernicus: A Brief Biography. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 4.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 5., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.193
    Synopsis: Nicolaus Copernicus: A Brief Biography -- Copernicus and Ibn al-Shir (d. 1375) Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 5.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 6., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.194
    Synopsis: Copernicus and Ibn al-Shir (d. 1375) Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 6.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 7 - Part 8., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.195
    Synopsis: The Many Different Copernican Revolutions -- Some Comments on Kuhn's View of Science -- De Revolutionibus Orbium Coelestium (1543): From Basic Ptolemaic to Basic Copernican --A New Result: Relative Orbital Radii -- Orbital Details: Eccentricity and the Equant. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 7 - 8.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 9., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.196
    Synopsis: Orbital Details: Eccentricity and the Equant -- Copernicus's System: the Three Motions -- Comments on Some Other Details of the System -- Copernicus's Triangulated Distances of the Planets. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 9.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 10., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.197
    Synopsis: Copernicus's Triangulated Distances of the Planets -- Philosophic Issue: Grounds for Preferring It? Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 10.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 11., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.198
    Synopsis: Philosophic Issue: Grounds for Preferring It? -- Another Answer: Opening a New Path for Research. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 11.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 12., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.199
    Synopsis: Another Answer: Opening a New Path for Research. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 12.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 13 - Part 14., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.200
    Synopsis: Tycho Brahe and Observational Astronomy -- Tycho Brahe and His Alternative System -- The Empirical Impasse in Astronomy -- The Value of More Precise Observations -- Tycho's Observational Program: 1576-1597 -- The Crisis in "Mathematical" Astronomy: The Three Chief World Systems in 1600. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 13 - 14.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 15., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.201
    Synopsis: The Crisis in "Mathematical" Astronomy: The Three Chief World Systems in 1600 -- Crisis: Epistemic Status of Astronomy -- The Crisis in Historical Context -- The Challenge: Empirical Evidence -- Select Sources. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 15.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Complete., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.202
    Synopsis: Prefatory Remarks: Some Background on Kepler -- Kepler and the Crisis in Mathematical Astronomy -- Kepler's Discovery of his Five Revolutionary Reforms in Orbital Theory -- Kepler's Original Justification for the Two "Laws" -- Select Sources. Section: Class 3, Complete.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 1., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.203
    Synopsis: Overview of the Class: Planetary Astronomy -- Turning Data into Evidence: Evidential Arguments -- The Kepler of Legend: A Contemporary Version. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 1.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 2., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.204
    Synopsis: The Kepler of Legend: A Contemporary Version -- Kepler: From Birth to Astronomia Nova, 1609 -- Kepler and the Crisis in Mathematical Astronomy -- Kepler's Response in the Apologia -- Kepler's Response in Astronomia Nova. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 2.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 3., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.205
    Synopsis: Kepler's Response in Astronomia Nova -- The Empirical Problem of Determining an Orbit. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 3.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 4 - Part 5., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.206
    Synopsis: The Empirical Problem of Determining an Orbit -- "Phase 0": On the Real versus the Mean Sun. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 4 - 5.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 6., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.207
    Synopsis: "Phase 0": On the Real versus the Mean Sun -- "Phase 1": An Account of the Latitudes -- "Phase 2": The "Vicarious Theory" Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 6.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 7., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.208
    Synopsis: "Phase 2": The "Vicarious Theory" -- "Phase 3": Bisect the Eccentricity of the Earth-Sun Orbit. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 7.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 8., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.209
    Synopsis: "Phase 3": Bisect the Eccentricity of the Earth-Sun Orbit. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 8.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 9., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.210
    Synopsis: "Phase 3": Bisect the Eccentricity of the Earth-Sun Orbit -- "Phase 3" Continued: the Area Rule. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 9.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 10., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.211
    Synopsis: "Phase 3" Continued: the Area Rule -- "Phase 4": The Orbit is Definitely Oval. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 10.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 11., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.212
    Synopsis: "Phase 4": The Orbit is Definitely Oval -- "Phase 5": Alternative Oval Trajectories -- "Phase 6": The Elliptical Trajectory. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 11.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 12., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.213
    Synopsis: "Phase 5": Alternative Oval Trajectories -- "Phase 6": The Elliptical Trajectory -- The Elliptical Trajectory and Diametral Distances -- "Phase 7": A Physical Explanation. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 12.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 13., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.214
    Synopsis: "Phase 6": The Elliptical Trajectory -- The Elliptical Trajectory and Diametral Distances -- "Phase 7": A Physical Explanation -- Kepler's Original Justification for the Two "Laws": The Context of Discovery versus the Context of Justification. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 13.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 14., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.215
    Synopsis: Kepler's Original Justification for the Two "Laws": The Context of Discovery versus the Context of Justification -- The Evidential Argument for the Latitudes of Mars -- The Evidential Argument for the Ellipse -- The Evidential Argument for the Area Rule -- Some Standard Objections to the Arguments -- A Contrasting View of Scientific Evidence -- A Defense of the Evidential Arguments for Mars -- Select Sources. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 14.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Complete., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.216
    Kepler's Astronomical Work Following Astronomia Nova -- Some Philosophic Issues Concerning Kepler's "Laws" -- An Examination of the Evidence for Kepler's "Laws" -- Kepler's Methodological Legacy: Some Final Remarks -- Select Sources. Section: Class 4, Complete.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 1 - Part 2., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.217
    Synopsis: The Orbital Innovations of Astronomia Nova -- The Achievement of Astronomia Nova: Summary Remarks. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 1 - 2.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 3., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.218
    Synopsis: The Achievement of Astronomia Nova: Summary Remarks. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 3.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 4., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.219
    Synopsis: Kepler: The Achievement of Astronomia Nova: Summary Remarks -- Kepler: The Subsequent Years (1609-1630) Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 4.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 5., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.220
    Synopsis: Kepler: The Subsequent Years (1609-1630) -- Mysterium Cosmigraphicum and Harmonice Mundi. Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 5.
  - Notes to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 6., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.221
    Synopsis: Kepler: The Subsequent Years (1609-1630) -- Mysterium Cosmigraphicum and Harmonice Mundi -- Kepler's Discovery of His Third "Law" (1618) -- Epitome Astronomiae Copernicanae (1618-1621) Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 6.